In part two of our interview with the creator and head of the U.S. government's largest acknowledged UAP study program, Dr. James Lukatsky.
The glory days of technologies were the 60s and 70s.
There were a lot of bright ideas and a lot of tests.
The Georgia case where the fella inadvertently hit, not inadvertently, he deliberately fired at a black triangle a million candle spotlight and it immediately fired back a radiation beam and he got tumors from it.
Through some investigative journalism over the years, I came to understand that you were read into and involved in a legacy UAP program before OSAP.
Do you deny that?
This is weaponized.
The following is part two of our interview with Dr. James Lukatsky.
I'm asking you about this crap.
I'm asking you, was it given to us?
Was it gifted to us?
Was it a crash?
You're going to get people mad at me for not answering when they know in advance and so do you that I can't answer.
And neither could they.
And neither can some of the people who are going before Congress.
They're putting pretty tight restrictions on.
On it if they do.
If they do go behind closed doors.
I'm saying the closed doors don't really matter in answering their question.
Okay, here's something you can't answer.
I imagine you can't answer to me if the craft had its own intelligence, if it was sentient in some way in and of itself.
You're not going to answer that, I assume, right?
So I got one you can't answer.
Last one, George, on this craft.
But I just got to ask these or I'm not doing my job.
You alluded that the UFO in the possession of the U.S.
makes.
The technology described in your other book, Initial Revelations, look primitive.
What did you mean by that?
It looks primitive.
Okay, but what does that mean to you?
It means it's very advanced.
And that's all I can say.
Very, very advanced.
And with worldwide repercussions.
Okay, but give me an idea I can sink my teeth into of what that means.
When you say very advanced.
I'm thinking, well, I've got an iPhone 17 and an original iPhone that's a big difference.
Are we talking, you know, sticks and stones to superconductors?
Advanced difference?
Absolutely.
Jim Lekatsky, you know, you said earlier in this conversation, I am for disclosure.
I'm not sure that has always been your position as Express Trust.
Maybe it was, but I got a different impression.
Do these books constitute disclosure?
I mean, these are.
This is in my opinion.
Yes, they are my disclosure, and they are the public's disclosure.
Remember, the public paid $22 million for the information.
The resulting information from OSAP is for the most, well, for 99% is releasable.
But here's another nitpick.
It's not a nitpick.
It's a fact.
The government owns the reports.
You've got to get it.
You've got to get it from the government, and you've got to have it cleansed by the government and checked by the government for public release.
I can't release to you the information.
If I would, I'd get a big stapler and and and staple all the documents together and give it to you.
And if if you wanted to try to interpret it, go ahead.
It's going to be difficult.
And that's also why, by the way, I broke up the technology portions into easy.
Engineering degree, physics degree or Ph.D.
And anyone who claims they understand all that is in those books for the technologies is fooling themselves.
They're certainly not fooling other technical people.
These reports are gathered from OSAP.
They're investigated.
They're checked out and vetted incidents, experiences, things of that sort from the official D.I.A. program.
They are approved.
through the DOPSER process. You are given permission to make this public. It is a form
of disclosure. Yes, it absolutely is. It may not be going as fast as people like, but
you really want to buy a war and peace or rise and fall of the Third Reich? How much would that
book cost? I mean, it has to be in a digestible amount. Somebody had to say yes to allow this.
Are you amazed that you're allowed to continue and spill some of this stuff, make it public?
Because you would think there's got to be people somewhere, maybe in Arrow, who are not
all that thrilled that it's coming out. I don't know if that's really the case. It's what comes
out and the detail of what comes out. Jeremy had said that before. It's like talking about
a nuclear weapon and then having the design blueprints and the fuel for the weapon.
There's a big difference there. I think this interview, I'm saying much more than the first
one. But the thing is, it's all still hasn't crossed the line. But I've got to ask what the
line is about future things. Because you're telling us UFOs, we have one, we're reverse
engineering it. But can you describe the inside? Can you talk about your personal
experience? Can you talk about your personal experience? Can you talk about your personal
experience with this crap, how you breached the hole? You don't know if you can say those
things yet. But certainly, they want us to know that much, not the nuclear codes, but the fact
nuclear weapons exist. Same thing about UFOs. Yes, I believe it'll go in the same way.
Yeah. And the thing is, is that now, there's some of this, the public has to, the public
scientists have to participate in. As I said, Kona Blue was a compartment reputed to be
for recovered technology. Okay. And then there's Kona Blue, the program, which was, in essence,
first described in, and I'm pointing up to a book sitting up there, Skinwalkers at the Pentagon.
Right. Because the private investment of money, we know that OSAP's not going to be repeated.
We know that. There's no way that's going to be repeated.
That focus on the paranormal and UFOs. So you got to learn now and then move on.
You can't say, well, I'm going to fund another OSAP too. No. And if anyone thinks that that was
the plan, well, they're wrong. Is there anything that you were told you can't say this about that
craft? Did you try to say more? And through the DOPSAR process,
they said, nope, that crosses the line. No, I didn't try to say more because I know
the rules and what they'd really deny. I will say there were some adjustments,
not severe, but adjustments to Skinwalkers at the Pentagon. In other words, take this out type
of adjustment. And I'm not talking about just names and academic institutions. We can't say
this. We can't.
here's something for jeremy we can't say this at that at this point but we did in the in the books
further on it's just you know it's like inch by inch you can't you're making it right you can't
eat the whole whale at once no i and look i really appreciate it i mean i see it as a heroic thing
that you're making these books and pushing each time to get a little further i don't i think
people don't understand that or they're very frustrated that you are take your oath seriously
but something you just mentioned that i think is a big point of yours that you haven't that we
haven't really um pushed on at this point i mean you basically ran the x-files for the u.s government
i mean it was it was pretty wild there were wild things that occurred but you said it best you said
a study focused solely on ufos on ver on various unknown nuts and bolts type craft
flittering around in the
skies over military bases and facilities would never get to the heart of a much larger and
complicated mystery and i think what you were trying to say to us is if you just think you're
going to study ufos you're going to be smacked with reality reality is the ufo phenomenon is
just shrouded and covered with what you would call i don't know the the good word abnormal
aspects of reality yes yes that you've got to look much further than nuts and bolts now
can
you study nuts and bolts and use it for a levitating craft would be tremendous doesn't
have to be a fast craft uh but 11 a levitating airliner think about the the where it could go
everywhere in the world it wouldn't need an airport but don't don't you think we've already
achieved that like we hear about all these people on military bases seeing triangles and you're
doing this study also to try to figure out the physics of how to do that do you think it's
already been achieved by the u.s government or it hasn't been achieved by the u.s government or it
hasn't been achieved by the u.s government or it hasn't been achieved by the u.s government or it hasn't
been achieved by the u.s government or it hasn't been achieved by the u.s government or it hasn't and that's why osap had a lot of
and that's why osap had a lot of
and that's why osap had a lot of value it hasn't been achieved to its full
value it hasn't been achieved to its full
value it hasn't been achieved to its full extent
extent
extent and uh by the way that's where uh
and uh by the way that's where uh
and uh by the way that's where uh a suggestion fronted by senator reed went
a suggestion fronted by senator reed went
a suggestion fronted by senator reed went into was
into was
into was i actually asked about your very question
i actually asked about your very question
i actually asked about your very question can we can we just cut through all this
can we can we just cut through all this
and do what we can do right now and check out this type of craft to the point of using all the money
just it's like it's like just make it putting all your chips on one because i said the breakthrough
would be tremendous if we can just pursue that um that wasn't funded either okay it was difficult
just make it you know senator reed got into a situation where people were turning down the money
one after another were turning down the money again doesn't that seem a bit odd a minority
leader and and then a former majority leader of the senate and they're turning